In 2049, World War III broke out.
The flames of nuclear war devoured the earth
and humans’ future.
A fatal plague, caused be a mutating virus,
is rapidly spreading over the post-apocalyptic world.
The world needs your help.
Now, play the role of a governor,
and take your duty to save the city and the people,
with limited resources and new technologies.
This is called “Age of Plague”.
In each level, the player initially has 10 cards
and he's allowed to replace at most 3 of them.
Each level corresponds to a city and contains cards peculiar to it.
For example, we are now in St. Petersburg.
Because of the high latitude,
the resources that can be harvested from land are very limited.
Therefore, people created a weather control system
to adapt to the environment,
which is represented by Blizzard and Drought.
The virus in the game spreads in a way
similar to that in Conway's game of life.
The player can view information of the virus.
As the player proceeds to next levels,
he gets more resources which allows him to draw and use more cards.
Danyu Zhou: Project 2 is no doubt hard and time consuming.
Without having effective teamwork,
it would be a lot harder for us
to create something equivalent to what we have accomplished now.
Jigang Li: In P2, I gained lots of experience in flat design.
And more importantly,
I gradually learned how to employ an adaptive workflow
not only as an individual, but also as a member of our team.
Haifeng Jia: Web designing is just amazing.
In the future, I will definitely study more knowledge
about front-end development.
Zefang Wei: Teamwork must be the most critical experience
in developing our project 2.
Despite difficulties and challenges,
we finally made it.
Enjoy our game!